http://www.isst-d.org/privacy-policy/

Become a MemberISSTDWorldSearchFacebookLinkedInInstagramTwitterMemberResourcesNon-Member ProfessionalResourcesPublicResourcesHome › Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the International Society for the Study of Trauma and Dissociation collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.isst-d.org website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by the International Society for the Study of Trauma and Dissociation.Personal Identification InformationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, complete a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features, or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, their name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and billing information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. A User can always decline to supply personally identifying information, though it should be noted that this may prevent said User from engaging in certain Site-related activities.Non-Personal Identification InformationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personally identifying information may include Users’ browser name, the type of computer or mobile device, and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet Service Providers utilized and other similar information.Web Browser CookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, it should be noted that some parts of the Site may not function as described or expected.Data CollectionThe International Society for the Study of Trauma and Dissociation may collect and use Users’ personal information for the following purposes:To run and operate our SiteWe may need User information to display content on the Site correctly.To improve customer serviceInformation Users provide helps us respond to their customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To provide membership benefitsInformation Users provide helps us deliver benefits associated with Society membership.To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To process paymentsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service related to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties, except to the extent necessary to provide the service.To send periodic emailsWe may use the User’s email address to send, to the User, information and updates pertaining to membership, training, conferences, product orders, and Society news.Data ProtectionWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data stored on our Site.Sharing Users’ Personal InformationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others without consent. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities, such as sending out newsletters or surveys, on our behalf,. We may share Users’ information with these third parties for those limited purposes only for those Users who have given us their permission.Electronic CommunicationsIf User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include Society news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. Alternately, User may contact us via email at info@isst-d.org to unsubscribe. Please allow 3-5 business days for changes to take effect once submitted. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share Users’ information with these third parties for those limited purposes, and only for Users who have given us their permission.Third Party WebsitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our supporters, exhibitors, advertisers, and/or other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.Changes to Privacy PolicyThe International Society for the Study of Trauma and Dissociation has full discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and revise the “updated on” date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect from Users. By using this Site, Users acknowledge and agree that it is their responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your Acceptance of These TermsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting ISSTDIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us via email at info@isst-d.org or via phone at 703-610-9037.This document was last updated on May 24, 2018
Due to the COVID-19 situation, ISSTD Staff is working remotely at this time. Phone lines will be open from 1:00–4:00pm Eastern Daylight Time Monday through Friday. Email is being monitored during normal business hours.
